[
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Special K\"?",
    "answer": "Greg Kelser",
    "choices": [
      "Dominique Wilkins",
      "Greg Kelser",
      "Michael Beasley",
      "John Salley"
    ],
    "additional info": "Greg Kelser is famously known as \"Special K\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Truck\"?",
    "answer": "Len Robinson",
    "choices": [
      "Pascal Siakam",
      "Len Robinson",
      "Fred Brown",
      "Lionel Hollins"
    ],
    "additional info": "Len Robinson is famously known as \"Truck\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Greyhound\"?",
    "answer": "Walter Davis",
    "choices": [
      "Walter Davis",
      "Kyrie Irving",
      "Ronald Jones",
      "Gilbert Arenas"
    ],
    "additional info": "Walter Davis is famously known as \"The Greyhound\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"World\"?",
    "answer": "Lloyd Bernard Free",
    "choices": [
      "Lloyd Bernard Free",
      "Dan Issel",
      "Larry Johnson",
      "Robert Parish"
    ],
    "additional info": "Lloyd Bernard Free is famously known as \"World\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Bam\"?",
    "answer": "Edrice Adebayo",
    "choices": [
      "Rodney Hundley",
      "Ricky Davis",
      "Edrice Adebayo",
      "Domantas Sabonis"
    ],
    "additional info": "Edrice Adebayo is famously known as \"Bam\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"El Chapo\"?",
    "answer": "James Harden",
    "choices": [
      "James Harden",
      "Larry Johnson",
      "Kevin Garnett",
      "Max Zaslofsky"
    ],
    "additional info": "James Harden is famously known as \"El Chapo\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"J-Dub\"?",
    "answer": "Jalen Williams",
    "choices": [
      "Jalen Williams",
      "Jerome Williams",
      "Tom Gugliotta",
      "Dwyane Wade"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jalen Williams is famously known as \"J-Dub\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Popeye\"?",
    "answer": "Ronald Jones",
    "choices": [
      "Darrell Griffith",
      "Nik Stauskas",
      "Iman Shumpert",
      "Ronald Jones"
    ],
    "additional info": "Ronald Jones is famously known as \"Popeye\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Jewish Jordan\"?",
    "answer": "Jon Scheyer",
    "choices": [
      "Anfernee Hardaway",
      "Jon Scheyer",
      "James Harden",
      "Robert Gruenig"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jon Scheyer is famously known as \"The Jewish Jordan\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Space-man\"?",
    "answer": "Sam Cassell",
    "choices": [
      "Sam Cassell",
      "Isiah Thomas",
      "Guerschon Yabusele",
      "Dalton Knecht"
    ],
    "additional info": "Sam Cassell is famously known as \"The Space-man\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Human Victory Cigar\"?",
    "answer": "Darko Miličić",
    "choices": [
      "Darko Miličić",
      "Rik Smits",
      "Shawn Bradley",
      "Tyrone Bogues"
    ],
    "additional info": "Darko Miličić is famously known as \"The Human Victory Cigar\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Ice\"?",
    "answer": "George Gervin",
    "choices": [
      "George Gervin",
      "Steve Francis",
      "Karl Malone",
      "Dan Majerle"
    ],
    "additional info": "George Gervin is famously known as \"Ice\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Nacho\"?",
    "answer": "Gilbert Arenas",
    "choices": [
      "Jonathon Simmons",
      "Max Zaslofsky",
      "Tom Hammonds",
      "Gilbert Arenas"
    ],
    "additional info": "Gilbert Arenas is famously known as \"Nacho\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Old Man Riverwalk\"?",
    "answer": "Tim Duncan",
    "choices": [
      "Steve Nash",
      "Tim Duncan",
      "Ersan İlyasova",
      "Guerschon Yabusele"
    ],
    "additional info": "Tim Duncan is famously known as \"Old Man Riverwalk\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Jellybean\"?",
    "answer": "Joe Bryant",
    "choices": [
      "Vitaly Potapenko",
      "Pervis Ellison",
      "Ben Wallace",
      "Joe Bryant"
    ],
    "additional info": "Joe Bryant is famously known as \"Jellybean\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Splash Brothers\"?",
    "answer": "Stephen Curry",
    "choices": [
      "Jerome Williams",
      "Stephen Curry",
      "Greg Monroe",
      "Yao Ming"
    ],
    "additional info": "Stephen Curry is famously known as \"Splash Brothers\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Spider\"?",
    "answer": "John Salley",
    "choices": [
      "Manu Ginóbili",
      "Mehmet Okur",
      "John Salley",
      "Bob Love"
    ],
    "additional info": "John Salley is famously known as \"Spider\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Gino\"?",
    "answer": "Manu Ginóbili",
    "choices": [
      "Manu Ginóbili",
      "Bob Dandridge",
      "Greg Monroe",
      "Steve Francis"
    ],
    "additional info": "Manu Ginóbili is famously known as \"Gino\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Red\"?",
    "answer": "John Graham Kerr",
    "choices": [
      "John Graham Kerr",
      "Guerschon Yabusele",
      "Richard Hamilton",
      "Nathaniel Clifton"
    ],
    "additional info": "John Graham Kerr is famously known as \"Red\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Big Ticket\"?",
    "answer": "Kevin Garnett",
    "choices": [
      "Jaylin Williams",
      "Fred Neal",
      "Michael Olowokandi",
      "Kevin Garnett"
    ],
    "additional info": "Kevin Garnett is famously known as \"Big Ticket\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Cuts\"?",
    "answer": "Isiah Thomas",
    "choices": [
      "Isiah Thomas",
      "Don Nelson",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Mitch Richmond"
    ],
    "additional info": "Isiah Thomas is famously known as \"Cuts\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"German Wunderkind\"?",
    "answer": "Dirk Nowitzki",
    "choices": [
      "Dirk Nowitzki",
      "Nik Stauskas",
      "Bradley Beal",
      "Theodore Edwards"
    ],
    "additional info": "Dirk Nowitzki is famously known as \"German Wunderkind\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Uncle Drew\"?",
    "answer": "Kyrie Irving",
    "choices": [
      "Robert Gruenig",
      "Brandon Ingram",
      "Luguentz Dort",
      "Kyrie Irving"
    ],
    "additional info": "Kyrie Irving is famously known as \"Uncle Drew\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Original Sun\"?",
    "answer": "Dick Van Arsdale",
    "choices": [
      "Jamal Crawford",
      "Dick Van Arsdale",
      "Darryl Dawkins",
      "Tom Sanders"
    ],
    "additional info": "Dick Van Arsdale is famously known as \"The Original Sun\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Mr. Buy 2 Get 1 Free\"?",
    "answer": "Shai Gilgeous-Alexander",
    "choices": [
      "Elliot Perry",
      "Dan Issel",
      "David Thompson",
      "Shai Gilgeous-Alexander"
    ],
    "additional info": "Shai Gilgeous-Alexander is famously known as \"Mr. Buy 2 Get 1 Free\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Time Lord\"?",
    "answer": "Robert Williams",
    "choices": [
      "Fred Hoiberg",
      "Paul Pierce",
      "Robert Williams",
      "Zydrunas Ilgauskas"
    ],
    "additional info": "Robert Williams is famously known as \"Time Lord\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Nasty Nick\"?",
    "answer": "Nick Van Exel",
    "choices": [
      "Julius Erving",
      "Greg Monroe",
      "Brent Barry",
      "Nick Van Exel"
    ],
    "additional info": "Nick Van Exel is famously known as \"Nasty Nick\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Great Wall of China\"?",
    "answer": "Yao Ming",
    "choices": [
      "Trajan Langdon",
      "Harold Miner",
      "Yao Ming",
      "Jonathan Isaac"
    ],
    "additional info": "Yao Ming is famously known as \"The Great Wall of China\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Coach K\"?",
    "answer": "Mike Krzyzewski",
    "choices": [
      "Luis Scola",
      "Mike Krzyzewski",
      "Tom Sanders",
      "Darryl Dawkins"
    ],
    "additional info": "Mike Krzyzewski is famously known as \"Coach K\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Bledshow\"?",
    "answer": "Eric Bledsoe",
    "choices": [
      "Greg Monroe",
      "Craig Claxton",
      "Eric Bledsoe",
      "Isiah Thomas"
    ],
    "additional info": "Eric Bledsoe is famously known as \"The Bledshow\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Stevie Franchise\"?",
    "answer": "Steve Francis",
    "choices": [
      "Steve Francis",
      "Jon Brockman",
      "Kristaps Porziņģis",
      "Josh Smith"
    ],
    "additional info": "Steve Francis is famously known as \"Stevie Franchise\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"El Contusione\"?",
    "answer": "Manu Ginóbili",
    "choices": [
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Jon Brockman",
      "Manu Ginóbili",
      "Giannis Antetokounmpo"
    ],
    "additional info": "Manu Ginóbili is famously known as \"El Contusione\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Timber\"?",
    "answer": "Ralph Siewert",
    "choices": [
      "Sam Cassell",
      "Tommy Heinsohn",
      "Fred Neal",
      "Ralph Siewert"
    ],
    "additional info": "Ralph Siewert is famously known as \"Timber\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"World B. Free\"?",
    "answer": "Lloyd Bernard Free",
    "choices": [
      "Lloyd Bernard Free",
      "Bobby Smith",
      "Pat Riley",
      "Jaylin Williams"
    ],
    "additional info": "Lloyd Bernard Free is famously known as \"World B. Free\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Zai\"?",
    "answer": "Isaiah Joe",
    "choices": [
      "Michael Beasley",
      "Isaiah Joe",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Matthew Dellavedova"
    ],
    "additional info": "Isaiah Joe is famously known as \"Zai\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Thief\"?",
    "answer": "Sedale Threatt",
    "choices": [
      "Sedale Threatt",
      "Anthony Jerome Webb",
      "Greg Kelser",
      "Gary Payton II"
    ],
    "additional info": "Sedale Threatt is famously known as \"The Thief\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Lonely Master\"?",
    "answer": "James Taft Fredette",
    "choices": [
      "Pascal Siakam",
      "James Taft Fredette",
      "Rasheed Wallace",
      "Lou Williams"
    ],
    "additional info": "James Taft Fredette is famously known as \"The Lonely Master\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"B-Easy\"?",
    "answer": "Michael Beasley",
    "choices": [
      "Sam Cassell",
      "Arvydas Sabonis",
      "Michael Beasley",
      "Steve Francis"
    ],
    "additional info": "Michael Beasley is famously known as \"B-Easy\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"J-Smoove\"?",
    "answer": "Josh Smith",
    "choices": [
      "Dean Meminger",
      "Chuck Person",
      "Dennis Rodman",
      "Josh Smith"
    ],
    "additional info": "Josh Smith is famously known as \"J-Smoove\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Jimmy Buckets\"?",
    "answer": "Jimmy Butler",
    "choices": [
      "Jim Pollard",
      "Jonathon Simmons",
      "Kenyon Martin",
      "Jimmy Butler"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jimmy Butler is famously known as \"Jimmy Buckets\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Maple Jordan\"?",
    "answer": "Andrew Wiggins",
    "choices": [
      "Shawn Bradley",
      "Lamar Odom",
      "John Wooden",
      "Andrew Wiggins"
    ],
    "additional info": "Andrew Wiggins is famously known as \"Maple Jordan\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Speedy\"?",
    "answer": "Craig Claxton",
    "choices": [
      "Greg Kelser",
      "Craig Claxton",
      "Maurice Stokes",
      "Jeremy Lin"
    ],
    "additional info": "Craig Claxton is famously known as \"Speedy\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Chris Paul\"?",
    "answer": "Rajon Rondo",
    "choices": [
      "Darryl Dawkins",
      "Rajon Rondo",
      "Jamal Murray",
      "Harry Gallatin"
    ],
    "additional info": "Rajon Rondo is famously known as \"Chris Paul\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Delly\"?",
    "answer": "Matthew Dellavedova",
    "choices": [
      "Matthew Dellavedova",
      "Paul Pierce",
      "Stephen Curry",
      "Harrison Barnes"
    ],
    "additional info": "Matthew Dellavedova is famously known as \"Delly\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Big Aristotle\"?",
    "answer": "Shaquille O'Neal",
    "choices": [
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Jason Williams",
      "Anthony Edwards",
      "Zydrunas Ilgauskas"
    ],
    "additional info": "Shaquille O'Neal is famously known as \"The Big Aristotle\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Hound\"?",
    "answer": "Jerry Baskerville",
    "choices": [
      "Jerry Baskerville",
      "Tyler Hansbrough",
      "Cedric Maxwell",
      "Andrew Toney"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jerry Baskerville is famously known as \"Hound\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Black Cat\"?",
    "answer": "Michael Jordan",
    "choices": [
      "John Havlicek",
      "E'Twaun Moore",
      "Larry Bird",
      "Michael Jordan"
    ],
    "additional info": "Michael Jordan is famously known as \"The Black Cat\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Sir Sid\"?",
    "answer": "Sidney Moncrief",
    "choices": [
      "Joe Caldwell",
      "Sidney Moncrief",
      "Chris Bosh",
      "DeMarcus Cousins"
    ],
    "additional info": "Sidney Moncrief is famously known as \"Sir Sid\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Dunkin' Dutchman\"?",
    "answer": "Rik Smits",
    "choices": [
      "Rudy Gobert",
      "Dan Issel",
      "Rik Smits",
      "Sofoklis Schortsianitis"
    ],
    "additional info": "Rik Smits is famously known as \"The Dunkin' Dutchman\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Gambler\"?",
    "answer": "Gilbert Arenas",
    "choices": [
      "Edrice Adebayo",
      "Joel Embiid",
      "Paul George",
      "Gilbert Arenas"
    ],
    "additional info": "Gilbert Arenas is famously known as \"The Gambler\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Manimal\"?",
    "answer": "Stacey Augmon",
    "choices": [
      "Ward Lambert",
      "Oscar Schmidt",
      "Karl Malone",
      "Stacey Augmon"
    ],
    "additional info": "Stacey Augmon is famously known as \"The Manimal\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Foul on You\"?",
    "answer": "Dwight Howard",
    "choices": [
      "Dick Van Arsdale",
      "Dwight Howard",
      "Boris Diaw",
      "Danilo Gallinari"
    ],
    "additional info": "Dwight Howard is famously known as \"Foul on You\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Splash Mountain\"?",
    "answer": "Brook Lopez",
    "choices": [
      "Brook Lopez",
      "Marcus Smart",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      "Robin Lopez"
    ],
    "additional info": "Brook Lopez is famously known as \"Splash Mountain\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Chocolate Thunder\"?",
    "answer": "Darryl Dawkins",
    "choices": [
      "Darryl Dawkins",
      "Jim Pollard",
      "Chauncey Billups",
      "Jamaal Wilkes"
    ],
    "additional info": "Darryl Dawkins is famously known as \"Chocolate Thunder\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Boy Gorge\"?",
    "answer": "Charles Barkley",
    "choices": [
      "Lance Stephenson",
      "William Holzman",
      "Anthony Jerome Webb",
      "Charles Barkley"
    ],
    "additional info": "Charles Barkley is famously known as \"Boy Gorge\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Big Dog\"?",
    "answer": "Glenn Robinson",
    "choices": [
      "Glenn Robinson",
      "Predrag Stojakovic",
      "Phil Jackson",
      "Tim Duncan"
    ],
    "additional info": "Glenn Robinson is famously known as \"Big Dog\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Swaggy P\"?",
    "answer": "Nick Young",
    "choices": [
      "Trevor Ariza",
      "Jalen Williams",
      "Theodore Edwards",
      "Nick Young"
    ],
    "additional info": "Nick Young is famously known as \"Swaggy P\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Mr. President\"?",
    "answer": "Bill Bradley",
    "choices": [
      "Maurice Stokes",
      "Lionel Hollins",
      "Bill Bradley",
      "Marvin Barnes"
    ],
    "additional info": "Bill Bradley is famously known as \"Mr. President\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Shaq\"?",
    "answer": "Shaquille O'Neal",
    "choices": [
      "Anthony Anderson",
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Bill Bradley",
      "Joe Bryant"
    ],
    "additional info": "Shaquille O'Neal is famously known as \"Shaq\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Meadowlark\"?",
    "answer": "Meadow Gerge Lemon",
    "choices": [
      "James Worthy",
      "Meadow Gerge Lemon",
      "Jamal Crawford",
      "Sidney Moncrief"
    ],
    "additional info": "Meadow Gerge Lemon is famously known as \"Meadowlark\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Riles\"?",
    "answer": "Pat Riley",
    "choices": [
      "Trajan Langdon",
      "Pat Riley",
      "Clyde Drexler",
      "Mike Krzyzewski"
    ],
    "additional info": "Pat Riley is famously known as \"Riles\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Horse\"?",
    "answer": "Dan Issel",
    "choices": [
      "Bob Love",
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Tommy Heinsohn",
      "Dan Issel"
    ],
    "additional info": "Dan Issel is famously known as \"The Horse\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Mailman\"?",
    "answer": "Karl Malone",
    "choices": [
      "Jeremy Lin",
      "Bill Bradley",
      "Chris Paul",
      "Karl Malone"
    ],
    "additional info": "Karl Malone is famously known as \"The Mailman\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Rip\"?",
    "answer": "Richard Hamilton",
    "choices": [
      "Richard Hamilton",
      "Henry Sims",
      "Stephon Marbury",
      "Theodore Edwards"
    ],
    "additional info": "Richard Hamilton is famously known as \"Rip\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Larry Legend\"?",
    "answer": "Larry Bird",
    "choices": [
      "Larry Bird",
      "Isaiah Joe",
      "Darko Miličić",
      "Billy Cunningham"
    ],
    "additional info": "Larry Bird is famously known as \"Larry Legend\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"C-Webb\"?",
    "answer": "Chris Webber",
    "choices": [
      "Boban Marjanović",
      "Earl Manigault",
      "Greg Monroe",
      "Chris Webber"
    ],
    "additional info": "Chris Webber is famously known as \"C-Webb\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Crisco Kid\"?",
    "answer": "Charles Barkley",
    "choices": [
      "Charles Barkley",
      "Daron Blaylock",
      "Pete Maravich",
      "Kawhi Leonard"
    ],
    "additional info": "Charles Barkley is famously known as \"The Crisco Kid\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Rock\"?",
    "answer": "Mitch Richmond",
    "choices": [
      "Karl Malone",
      "Furkan Korkmaz",
      "Mitch Richmond",
      "Mike Krzyzewski"
    ],
    "additional info": "Mitch Richmond is famously known as \"The Rock\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Beli\"?",
    "answer": "Marco Belinelli",
    "choices": [
      "Isiah Thomas",
      "Andrea Bargnani",
      "Marco Belinelli",
      "Lamar Odom"
    ],
    "additional info": "Marco Belinelli is famously known as \"Beli\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Il Gallo\"?",
    "answer": "Danilo Gallinari",
    "choices": [
      "Danilo Gallinari",
      "Daron Blaylock",
      "Domantas Sabonis",
      "Robert Williams"
    ],
    "additional info": "Danilo Gallinari is famously known as \"Il Gallo\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Crawssover Crawford\"?",
    "answer": "Jamal Crawford",
    "choices": [
      "Michael Beasley",
      "Jamal Crawford",
      "Xavier McDaniel",
      "Nate Archibald"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jamal Crawford is famously known as \"Crawssover Crawford\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Natural\"?",
    "answer": "Brandon Roy",
    "choices": [
      "Vince Carter",
      "Brandon Roy",
      "Pascal Siakam",
      "Jerome Richardson"
    ],
    "additional info": "Brandon Roy is famously known as \"The Natural\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Butch\"?",
    "answer": "Alfred Beard",
    "choices": [
      "Iman Shumpert",
      "Ruben Patterson",
      "Alfred Beard",
      "Jeremy Lin"
    ],
    "additional info": "Alfred Beard is famously known as \"Butch\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Big Country\"?",
    "answer": "Bryant Reeves",
    "choices": [
      "Joe Bryant",
      "Daron Blaylock",
      "Bryant Reeves",
      "John Salley"
    ],
    "additional info": "Bryant Reeves is famously known as \"Big Country\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Fat\"?",
    "answer": "Lafayette Lever",
    "choices": [
      "Lafayette Lever",
      "Zydrunas Ilgauskas",
      "Clarence Francis",
      "Furkan Korkmaz"
    ],
    "additional info": "Lafayette Lever is famously known as \"Fat\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Steph\"?",
    "answer": "Stephen Curry",
    "choices": [
      "Andre Drummond",
      "Marcus Smart",
      "Danilo Gallinari",
      "Stephen Curry"
    ],
    "additional info": "Stephen Curry is famously known as \"Steph\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Beard\"?",
    "answer": "James Harden",
    "choices": [
      "Ed Macauley",
      "James Harden",
      "John Salley",
      "Predrag Stojakovic"
    ],
    "additional info": "James Harden is famously known as \"The Beard\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Acrobatic from the Democratic\"?",
    "answer": "Bismack Biyombo",
    "choices": [
      "Bismack Biyombo",
      "Tyrone Bogues",
      "Mitch Richmond",
      "Craig Claxton"
    ],
    "additional info": "Bismack Biyombo is famously known as \"The Acrobatic from the Democratic\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"KryptoNate\"?",
    "answer": "Nate Robinson",
    "choices": [
      "Vinnie Johnson",
      "Glen Davis",
      "Earl Manigault",
      "Nate Robinson"
    ],
    "additional info": "Nate Robinson is famously known as \"KryptoNate\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Shnaq\"?",
    "answer": "Shaquille O'Neal",
    "choices": [
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Vinnie Johnson",
      "Oscar Robertson",
      "Rajon Rondo"
    ],
    "additional info": "Shaquille O'Neal is famously known as \"The Shnaq\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Blind Bomber\"?",
    "answer": "George Glamack",
    "choices": [
      "George Glamack",
      "Rudy Gobert",
      "Gerald Wallace",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
    ],
    "additional info": "George Glamack is famously known as \"The Blind Bomber\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The G.O.A.T\"?",
    "answer": "Michael Jordan",
    "choices": [
      "Danilo Gallinari",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Craig Smith",
      "Jason Kidd"
    ],
    "additional info": "Michael Jordan is famously known as \"The G.O.A.T\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Big Shot Rob\"?",
    "answer": "Robert Horry",
    "choices": [
      "Tom Sanders",
      "Julius Randle",
      "Charles Barkley",
      "Robert Horry"
    ],
    "additional info": "Robert Horry is famously known as \"Big Shot Rob\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Boom\"?",
    "answer": "Jaylin Williams",
    "choices": [
      "Jaylin Williams",
      "Kurt Thomas",
      "Artis Gilmore",
      "Mikal Bridges"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jaylin Williams is famously known as \"Boom\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Downtown Freddie\"?",
    "answer": "Fred Brown",
    "choices": [
      "Sam Cassell",
      "Fred Brown",
      "Maurice Stokes",
      "Arvydas Sabonis"
    ],
    "additional info": "Fred Brown is famously known as \"Downtown Freddie\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Clever\"?",
    "answer": "James Worthy",
    "choices": [
      "James Worthy",
      "Earvin Johnson",
      "Derrick Chievous",
      "Latrell Sprewell"
    ],
    "additional info": "James Worthy is famously known as \"Clever\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Waiter\"?",
    "answer": "Toni Kukoc",
    "choices": [
      "Anthony Jerome Webb",
      "Buddy Hield",
      "Bob Dandridge",
      "Toni Kukoc"
    ],
    "additional info": "Toni Kukoc is famously known as \"The Waiter\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Pistol Pete\"?",
    "answer": "Pete Maravich",
    "choices": [
      "Dean Meminger",
      "Alfred Beard",
      "Gerald Wallace",
      "Pete Maravich"
    ],
    "additional info": "Pete Maravich is famously known as \"Pistol Pete\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Deebo\"?",
    "answer": "DeMar DeRozan",
    "choices": [
      "DeMar DeRozan",
      "Markelle Fultz",
      "Kenrich Williams",
      "Earl Monroe"
    ],
    "additional info": "DeMar DeRozan is famously known as \"Deebo\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Dirty\"?",
    "answer": "Dirk Nowitzki",
    "choices": [
      "Dennis Rodman",
      "Karl-Anthony Towns",
      "Dirk Nowitzki",
      "Isaiah Joe"
    ],
    "additional info": "Dirk Nowitzki is famously known as \"Dirty\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Knick Killer\"?",
    "answer": "Reggie Miller",
    "choices": [
      "Anthony Jerome Webb",
      "Joe Bryant",
      "Reggie Miller",
      "Chauncey Billups"
    ],
    "additional info": "Reggie Miller is famously known as \"The Knick Killer\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Super Mario\"?",
    "answer": "Mario Hezonja",
    "choices": [
      "Chris Webber",
      "Billy Cunningham",
      "Mario Hezonja",
      "Gary Payton"
    ],
    "additional info": "Mario Hezonja is famously known as \"Super Mario\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Shump\"?",
    "answer": "Iman Shumpert",
    "choices": [
      "Iman Shumpert",
      "George Glamack",
      "Vernal Coles",
      "Anthony Anderson"
    ],
    "additional info": "Iman Shumpert is famously known as \"Shump\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Beastbrook\"?",
    "answer": "Russell Westbrook",
    "choices": [
      "Ralph Siewert",
      "Kevin Porter",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "Marcin Gortat"
    ],
    "additional info": "Russell Westbrook is famously known as \"Beastbrook\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"J Crossover\"?",
    "answer": "Jamal Crawford",
    "choices": [
      "Kemba Walker",
      "Bob Love",
      "Jamal Crawford",
      "Toni Kukoc"
    ],
    "additional info": "Jamal Crawford is famously known as \"J Crossover\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Hartenstein's Monster\"?",
    "answer": "Isaiah Hartenstein",
    "choices": [
      "Ersan İlyasova",
      "Theodore Edwards",
      "Isaiah Hartenstein",
      "Derrick Chievous"
    ],
    "additional info": "Isaiah Hartenstein is famously known as \"Hartenstein's Monster\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"The Black Hole\"?",
    "answer": "Kevin McHale",
    "choices": [
      "Shai Gilgeous-Alexander",
      "Mario Hezonja",
      "Jon McGlocklin",
      "Kevin McHale"
    ],
    "additional info": "Kevin McHale is famously known as \"The Black Hole\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Super Cool Beas\"?",
    "answer": "Michael Beasley",
    "choices": [
      "Michael Beasley",
      "John Havlicek",
      "Sofoklis Schortsianitis",
      "Daron Blaylock"
    ],
    "additional info": "Michael Beasley is famously known as \"Super Cool Beas\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"Joker\"?",
    "answer": "Nikola Jokić",
    "choices": [
      "Andrew Wiggins",
      "Nikola Jokić",
      "Ralph Siewert",
      "Zach Randolph"
    ],
    "additional info": "Nikola Jokić is famously known as \"Joker\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which NBA player is known by the nickname \"El Sid\"?",
    "answer": "Sidney Moncrief",
    "choices": [
      "Stojko Vranković",
      "Jaylin Williams",
      "Sidney Moncrief",
      "Rasheed Wallace"
    ],
    "additional info": "Sidney Moncrief is famously known as \"El Sid\"",
    "difficulty": "Medium",
    "era": "All Time"
  }
]